storenvy.com 2015-12-04

# STORENVY | Privacy Policy

Storenvy knows that you care how information about you is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so with care and sensitivity.

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) covers the use of the website located at www.storenvy.com and the services provided by Storenvy (sometimes herein “Storenvy,” “We” or “Us”), including how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. This Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Storenvy does not own or control, or individuals that we do not employ or manage.

Storenvy is occasionally known to speak in the rare dialect known as “legalese,” such as on this page. Please bear with Us as We do so. 

### Information Collection and How it is Used

Storenvy will not sell or disclose your name or email address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this Privacy Policy.

Storenvy collects personal information when you register to use our services or to post content on our site. At registration you are asked for a username, password and a valid email address.

If you would like to obtain a Storenvy custom storefront, we will ask for your store name, a [Stripe](http://www.stripe.com/) account, and store URL. You also have the option to use PayPal for your custom storefront in addition to Stripe. We will not have access to either your PayPal or Stripe account. 

Storenvy automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies and the pages you request. This data is only used in the aggregate.

Storenvy uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a webpage. Your IP address is stored in Storenvy’s user registration databases when you register with us. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes. 

### Service-related Announcements

Storenvy will send you a welcome/confirmation email when you sign up for our services. Confirmation of this email is required for using opening a Storenvy storefront, but not for the use of any other features of the site.

Storenvy will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.

You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Storenvy products or services that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Storenvy service. Storenvy uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you “sign in”; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Storenvy’s services; display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on Storenvy; estimate and report Storenvy’s total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve Storenvy’s content and services.

Storenvy cookies do not collect personal information, and Storenvy does not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your username or email address is. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

When you post a message, your Storenvy username is visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Storenvy may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Storenvy Terms of Service. Storenvy may disclose personally identifiable information as our sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, Storenvy may disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name. Storenvy may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

Storenvy may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and needs to share your information with them to provide products and services to you. Examples include but are not limited to fulfilling orders, handling billing disputes and collections, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service.

Storenvy will not rent, sell or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when Storenvy has your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Storenvy Terms of Use, as specified in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by law. In some cases, Storenvy may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Storenvy will transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Storenvy website before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

As part of the buying and selling process, you may obtain another Storenvy user’s email address, shipping address and/or other information. This information should only be used for Storenvy-related communications or for Stornenvy-facilitated transactions. Storenvy has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without limiting the foregoing, without express consent from the user, you are not licensed to add any Storenvy user to your email or physical mail list.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and Storenvy’s ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order, legal process, or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to protect Storenvy’s rights, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or to report suspected illegal activity.

This Policy is effective March 1, 2009, for current users, and upon acceptance for new users.
